[Music]
Just look, use your hands when driving. Wear a helmet. Whenever you go outside,
say wear a helmet. Whenever you turn around, wear a helmet.
[Music]
Hello friends, today in my video I
want to tell all the children and adults that
every hour four people are dying in India
due to not wearing a helmet. According to the report of India Today,
during 2021,
7,000 people were claimed to have died in accidents in the country.
In 2021, [
Music]
15562 people lost their lives due to road accidents.
Drive slowly, not for yourself, but for your
family.
ISI Mark Navad. Those who had
subscribed to our previous blog,
please like,
subscribe and share this blog also. We do
not need a helmet. It is good for our safety.
Now you tell me, when you
drive, a helmet is a vehicle's
helmet,
our friends.